900 million dollar bill
9亿美元的法案
dangerous situations
险情
Cabas have been feeling the heat in Nissan months is Siri prices has salt do to supply Titanic deleted
的Cabas一直感觉热的日产月是Siri的价格已经做盐供应泰坦尼克删除
Siri prices reaching level prices for big c*** $90
Siri的价格达到一级价格大C ***90美元
if we proceed the plan NBC Charlotte Michigan speech on the number 15 percent indeed the pocket
如果我们继续进行该计划的NBC密歇根州夏洛特言论上的数字15％确实是口袋
xi complexity t got
喜复杂吨得到
possibilities to decipher the club Vegas you est HS been on the way since April content Nickelback is to come to an oversupply of you eat between 2008 and 2009
可能性破译俱乐部拉斯维加斯你一直在路上，因为四月含量Nickelback乐队是来为你供过于求东部时间HS吃2008年和2009年间
cheap and say that if you committed to Hyatt Hotel number to call to see the market expected in Siri prices
价格便宜，说，如果你致力于凯悦酒店要拨打的号码，看看预期的Siri价格市场
50 cent diss the Jackson had been taken Aaliyah
50美分迪斯杰克逊已经采取艾莉亚
still some potential Cabas tote dimensions will be implemented
仍然有一些潜在的Cabas手提包尺寸将实施
movies with people who buy collar help
电影的人谁买的衣领帮助
siding many people young children
壁板很多人幼儿
as a cell to boost in the series Supply b16 turbo
作为细胞在系列供应B16涡轮增压
expected competed study of the possible missions TN
可能的任务TN的预期竞争研究
delete all so says the government and Trina polices will Spano FL making the Veil system more reliable speaking at the groundbreaking ceremony for the 12 West extension reset this is a top priority
删除所有这样说，政府和天合光能政策将斯帕诺FL使得面纱系统更加可靠在讲为12西延重置奠基仪式，这是重中之重
easier to commute to the area has begun 4 station the Argyle Circle 12 Crescent Road and West links to be a 2600 decals
容易通勤到该地区已经开始4站亚皆老街12圈坊路和西环节是一个2600贴花
extension is expected to benefit more than 100
扩展有望受益100多
even if the real network is being extended capacity will also be approved in the coming yes mulching sub Eng to kill the second line
即使真正的网络正在扩大，在未来是覆盖子工程能力也将得到批准杀二线
will give up by 60 percent of 24 mochi recipe from taking 1558 mochi
会放弃60％的24年糕食谱服用1558麻糬
Transport Minister note to the consent of the series strange attractions in Houston months citizen Mikey will putting Jace Amaro bus system
交通部长照会的一系列奇怪的景点休斯顿几个月公民米奇将会把杰斯阿马罗总线系统的同意
potential foot tease in the system listen to announce 900 million dollar tan to upgrade the new 18 SS
潜在的脚挑逗系统中的听，宣布9亿美元的棕褐色升级新18 SS
mystery set to main components of Virginia
神秘设为弗吉尼亚主要成分
one piece in the steepest the track what is it is a breeding of the singing sisters he said the land transport Texarkana Cinemark eat in the process of making sure that each party will take a fashion
在最陡峭的一块轨道是什么是歌唱姐妹，他说，在确保各方将采取的方式的过程中，陆路运输特克萨卡纳喜满吃的繁殖
on with the Colts will eventually be possible to commute is at high assists 36 says that determined by to fit a justmine formula which is being reviewed to reset fast would not be a justice issue of us on the Wii
与小马队最终将有可能改判为高助攻36表示，由下式确定，以适应正在被审查，以快速恢复，一justmine公式不会是我们在Wii上一个正义问题
will still on MIT trains SMRT is looking into making several improvements of major functions in December the end of the third week of the Committee of Inquiry hearing
仍然会在麻省理工学院的培训SMRT正在考虑制定的主要功能一些改进十二月研讯委员会第三周结束
December destructions put the spotlight on the way to the marquee handle the situation directions train operation Sharon Abdul Salam told committee that there are several areas of improvement smot is working on
十二月毁灭把目光对准的方式向选取框处理情况方向列车运行莎朗·阿卜杜勒·萨拉姆告诉委员会，有改善SMOT正致力于多个领域
one is and you dedicate a communications T Mobile train service controllers Pacific possible be in charge of giving information to passengers from the operations control center
一个是，你奉献一个通信T移动一条龙服务控制器太平洋可能负责从业务提供乘客信息控制中心
another is a public announcement guide for train offices how soon train offices should an ounce of destruction
另一种是公告指南火车办事处如何尽快火车办事处应销毁的一盎司
what they should say another area bean look into act suna in telling passengers to get off the train instead of the current standard operating procedure of 45 minutes it should be 30 minutes the train operators also looking into making small improvement
他们应该说的另一个领域豆直视行为苏纳在告诉乘客下车，而不是45分钟的现行标准操作程序应该是30分钟的火车运营商也正在研究制定小的提升下车
on December 15 some type of doctors and complain to prevent elation
12月15日某种类型的医生和抱怨，以防止得意洋洋
Sharon told committee assigned telling passengers to use the emergency in Tacoma the need to speak to the train officer Lil B installed to allow passengers to inform the office at the note is the lights of ventilation have gone off
沙龙对分配告诉乘客使用紧急塔科马委员会一定要发言火车官律：B安装的，让乘客告知办公室在说明的是通风的灯光已经熄灭
Justin's raised by the Committee of the day this include installing a sensor on emoji trains to detect if connected shoes which pickup power from the Sun trail a damaged
Justin的通过一天的委员会提出了这个包括表情符号列车上安装一个传感器，以检测是否连接鞋从太阳跟踪皮卡电源损坏
SMRT projects and technology stop humping hold it would be useful phrases concerned Mike overwhelmed train operators is a have too many of
SMRT项目和技术站驼峰持有这将是有关迈克不堪重负列车运营有用的短语是有太多的
China has opens door to resolve intentions of activist Chen Guangcheng paging system is free to apply to study abroad US Secretary of State
中国已经打开大门，以解决活动家陈光诚寻呼系统的意图是免费申请出国留学美国国务卿
she's in college by China statement Washington China have a great movie quotes expeditiously to provide the necessary travel documents to chin and his family
她在大学由中国报表华盛顿中国有一个伟大的电影对白迅速提供必要的旅行证件，以下巴和他的家人
the development
发展
49.wav
from Django Unchained hospital bed details are emerging about his concerns over his safety and that of his family and supporters
从Django的奔放医院病床上的细节不断涌现对他担忧他的安全，他的家人和支持者
John even manage to phone into a US congressional hearing on his case to appeal to help
约翰甚至设法打电话到他的案子在美国国会听证会上呼吁帮助
cinzetti has invested in 10 yes and that he wants to go to the United States for a few months
cinzetti已投资10是，他要去美国了几个月
China of an apparent concession saying that you can apply to study abroad one of his supporters his chin has an invitation from New York University
一个明显的让步对中国说，你可以申请出国留学他的支持者之一，他的下巴有纽约大学的邀请
the Toledo show me young do the polls for the 2012
托莱多告诉我年轻做的民意调查，为2012年
the US came in for strong criticism Nova how it handle the situation staging has the modded an apology from Washington
美国进来的强烈批评新星是如何处理这种情况分期已经在华盛顿改装成一个道歉
of course United States continues to raise human rights because we believe that says they are essential for every country
当然，美国继续提出人权，因为我们相信，说他们是每个国家至关重要
hold it comes as new reports of a dramatic details after how many have reached the US Embassy of escaping house arrest New York Times account is the embassy Santa come to pick up in an alleyway even as Chinese Ortiz gay chase
拿着它之后有多少人达到逃脱软禁的美国大使馆纽约时报帐户是使馆圣诞老人来接在一个小巷甚至是中国奥尔蒂斯同性恋追来作为一个戏剧性的细节新报告
the use of legal to leave the self confessed monstermind of the temperature in 11th Terrace tax in full color to use will be formally of rain tomorrow for military commission in Guantanamo Bay
运用法律留下的温度自认monstermind在第11露台税全彩使用将正式的雨明天在关塔那摩湾军事委员会
Harlem shake Muhammad and his co conspirators will be charged with planning and executing the attacks at nextmuni Suites Thousand people dead in New York Washington and Pennsylvania
哈林摇穆罕默德和他的同谋的合作将负责规划和执行攻击在nextmuni套房千人死在纽约，华盛顿和宾夕法尼亚州
Facebook death sentences if convicted
Facebook的死刑判决，如果罪名成立
the trial itself could still be months away that the defendant pleads guilty
审判本身可能仍然是个月的时间，被告认罪
Malaysia details of a Dutch boys 6th day kitchen Apple deal with parents say the kidnappers took care of 12 year old Nyack he would be a vet him even allowed him to take a shower
荷兰男孩第6天厨苹果对付父母的马来西亚细节说绑匪拿了12岁尼亚克照顾他会成为一名兽医他甚至让他洗澡
believe 7th through a party for the community to celebrate the Sun safer to turn on Home Dr the paid an undisclosed when something is father of a twin sister and mom sex in his bed on his back
通过党，为社会相信第七庆祝太阳更安全打开主页的医生什么时候是一个双胞胎姐姐和妈妈做爱在他的床上在他的背上的父亲支付了未公开
posted this picture of a man with the run across the street and try to stop my ass is Kannapolis he called John Daly a brave heart for what he did
发布这张照片的人与街对面的运行和试图阻止我的屁股是坎纳波利斯，他叫约翰 - 达利勇敢的心脏为他做了什么
coming up on you find fire break out into separate incident in several people be like
你来了发现火灾闯入了另一起事件中有几个人会喜欢
how to get the police
如何让警察
extinguished in 15 minutes
熄灭15分钟
the group of writing it down town east has been sentenced to 5 years jail and 6th Ave KC
该集团把它写下来镇东部已被判处5年监禁和第六大道KC
lashton stabbed with knife chocolate and a screwdriver who died of multiple injuries wale sopita guilty to a separate charge of punching a Korean national at a nightclub
lashton用刀插巧克力和一把螺丝刀向谁冲压韩国国民在一家夜总会的单独收费死于多处受伤纵行sopita犯
the one US is the general election definition communications and Beyond Kobe Bryant says he seems changes into areas in Singapore Italian coffee this afternoon he said when is the area of engagement with the government has stepped up at South Beach FL
一个是美国的大选定义通信和超越科比说，他似乎变成新加坡的意大利咖啡区今天下午，他说当参与与政府的地区加强了在南佛罗里达州海滩
note that more people are using you platforms that the government has created from social media Facebook and Twitter to get information in News
注意，越来越多的人正在使用您的政府已经从社交媒体Facebook和Twitter建立的获取信息的新闻平台
find out if you insult
发现，如果你侮辱
because you recognize that is cheap trianex effective change music teacher f****** to the gnome something we have to communicate
因为你认识到是便宜trianex有效改变音乐老师F ******到GNOME的东西，我们必须沟通
the most attractive jobs in Singapore reportedly in the hospitality and recreational industries according to an online services provided that which pulled 4000 please in December
根据在线服务在新加坡最有吸引力的工作据说在酒店和娱乐行业的规定，从而拉升4000，请在十二月
nearly 14 tens and incenter the sex in office interesting job contest
近14几万，并在内心办公有趣的工作竞赛性
1210 believed to Pleasant looking at p**** a HR petition to see the findings Bodwell for the 76 to riches seeking to check the individuals to shine customer service
1210信喜看为p ****一个人力资源请愿书，看看结果Bodwell为76到财富寻求检查个人照耀客户服务
Hotel sea disposal scene success in retaining Wolcott
海酒店现场处置成功留住沃尔科特
create environment that people do not want to leave now sometimes I lay Gingerman find the graph on a little greener on the other side greener pastures Academy Anderson time
创造环境，人们不想现在就离开，有时我躺在姜饼找到另一边择木而栖奥斯卡·安德森时间一点点绿色的曲线图
why we have a reputation out in Singapore and we have a club called the boomerang club and we have over now a hundred twenty a violation John the grass is greener on the other side they gone off and within a year to year State comeback
为什么我们的声誉在新加坡，我们有一个俱乐部叫回旋镖俱乐部，我们有超过现在一百二十违反约翰草更绿的，他们出去了，在一年之内，以每年国家卷土重来的另一面
Hospitality and recreational industries highest significance number for look at the government is the number to the country to be sick
为看政府招待和娱乐行业的最高意义号码是该国生病
expect the face challenges ficiency companies need to build on employment branding attract more local
预计，面对挑战FICIENCY公司需要建立对就业的品牌吸引更多本地
the ranch at 720 to shoot that employs rank the financial health of the company has the top priority when choosing an employer this is a long time job security and competitive salary and benefits
牧场在720拍，它采用排名公司的财务健康状况具有头等大事时，选择一个雇主，这是很长一段时间的工作保障和有竞争力的薪酬和福利
will he will be looking for a job anytime soon but an Australian man has become the world's oldest graduate for the second time
将他将会很快找了工作，但一名澳大利亚男子已成为世界上最古老的研究生的第二次
South Wales the brakes on 2006 at the age of 91 dentist degree and its time does in clinical science
南威尔士州在91牙医程度和时间的年龄在2006年刹车确实在临床科学
studying is easier now compared to 7 decades ago when he completed his first degree with the aid of Technology teaspoons to our computer each morning and afternoon for distance learning
学习是现在比较容易对比7十年前，当他每天早晨和下午的远程学习完成了他的第一个学位与技术茶匙的援助，我们的计算机
lifelong student says this is his last
终身学生说，这是他最后一次
Donna from the family guys
唐娜从家庭人
and with six children 12 grandchildren and six great grandchildren he's got plenty to keep an occupied
并与六个孩子12个孙子和6个曾孙他有很多可以让一个被占领
14615 from cold
14615从冷
business news 88
每日经济新闻88
social networking Giants Facebook set a price based on the 28th
社交网络巨头Facebook的设置的基础上，28日的价格
Facebook 11.8 about 14.67 1515 State Street
Facebook的约11.8 14.67 1515国街
NBC Sports Malaysian Superleague Lions 12
NBC体育马来西亚超级联赛12狮
justified election in a foot Joyce's what state has the best chances of the gate shopping
在一只脚乔伊斯的状态是什么理由选的门购物的最佳机会
Facebook
Facebook的
side
侧
Spanish football that was a message to eat near the fountain
西班牙足球，这是一个消息在喷泉附近吃
AAA captain d Kaka SIA title Club flag around the Statue of the Sui championship
周围的隋总冠军的雕像AAA队长Ð卡卡新航冠军俱乐部标志
national symbols
国家象征
tomorrow is Fight Night at the base Anne Hathaway in the Dragonfire championship boxing Chinese opponent
明天是搏击之夜在基地安妮·海瑟薇在龙火拳击锦标赛中国对手
710 to start a traction Chris John
710启动牵引力克里斯·约翰
InStyle the Indonesian is defending his World Boxing Association superworld featherweight title going up against Japan Shoji to be to 4000 tickets have been sold
造我的印尼是捍卫他的世界拳击协会superworld轻量级冠军将打击日本商事是到4000门票已售出
Asia has launched a brand new Apple iPad and iPhone uses every place is an existing app which has backed up more than 500
亚洲已经推出了全新的苹果iPad和iPhone使用的每一个地方是一个现有的应用程序，这已经备份了500多
the new Channel NewsAsia app office in Mobile AL news experience uses can juices can the news of the day in pictures and reviews customizable this also real time news taka
在莫比尔新闻体验新亚洲新闻频道办公应用程序可以使用果汁可以在一天中的图片和评论的新闻定制，这也实时新闻塔卡
uses to be consumed when you want it animal license allow you to do so that anytime of the day in any place menu tight to a second location to the office PC audio to TV setup
使用时，你想让它动物许可证允许你紧张这么做的一天，任何时候在任何地方菜单到第二个位置到办公室PC音频到电视设置被消耗